[{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":14521,"timeElapsed":124600},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980350483,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":19259,"timeElapsed":143860},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":10290,"timeElapsed":154152},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":13537,"timeElapsed":167689},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8370,"timeElapsed":176061},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":13250,"timeElapsed":189313},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5477,"timeElapsed":194792},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6864,"timeElapsed":201657},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980415193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"8","question":"Name three things you and your closest friend or partner have in common.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":6911,"timeElapsed":208570},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":18066,"timeElapsed":227806},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980438182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3752,"timeElapsed":231559},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4018,"timeElapsed":235579},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6415,"timeElapsed":241995},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6331,"timeElapsed":248327},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980462361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":7410,"timeElapsed":255738},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980470467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":8105,"timeElapsed":263844},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5001,"timeElapsed":268847},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980479134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3663,"timeElapsed":272511},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":12389,"timeElapsed":286154},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3234,"timeElapsed":289389},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4926,"timeElapsed":294316},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980505362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4421,"timeElapsed":298739},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":9225,"timeElapsed":307965},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3466,"timeElapsed":311433},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":9417,"timeElapsed":320851},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5541,"timeElapsed":326393},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":4407,"timeElapsed":330802},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980549724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":11123,"timeElapsed":343101},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5711,"timeElapsed":348813},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10761,"timeElapsed":359574},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4448,"timeElapsed":364023},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4688,"timeElapsed":368712},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3902,"timeElapsed":372614},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980590245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":11007,"timeElapsed":383622},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3158,"timeElapsed":386781},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10494,"timeElapsed":397276},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980615983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":10799,"timeElapsed":409360},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980623401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7417,"timeElapsed":416778},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4932,"timeElapsed":421711},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3833,"timeElapsed":425545},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980636235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4066,"timeElapsed":429612},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3390,"timeElapsed":433004},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980643626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3998,"timeElapsed":437003},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4550,"timeElapsed":441554},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7444,"timeElapsed":448999},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980666663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":10205,"timeElapsed":460040},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2653,"timeElapsed":462693},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2668,"timeElapsed":465363},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980681736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":9750,"timeElapsed":475113},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980708042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":26305,"timeElapsed":501419},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":12389,"timeElapsed":513810},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726485,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6051,"timeElapsed":519862},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980729569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3083,"timeElapsed":522946},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980732735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3165,"timeElapsed":526112},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980748657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":14558,"timeElapsed":542034},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980751932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3274,"timeElapsed":545309},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980754287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2353,"timeElapsed":547664},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980762613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":8324,"timeElapsed":555990},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980769662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7047,"timeElapsed":563039},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5601,"timeElapsed":568641},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6244,"timeElapsed":574886},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980790583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":9072,"timeElapsed":583960},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":6564,"timeElapsed":590525},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980817784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":19256,"timeElapsed":611161},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980821251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3466,"timeElapsed":614628},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980826117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4864,"timeElapsed":619494},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980829420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3302,"timeElapsed":622797},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980846119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":16698,"timeElapsed":639496},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980850956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4834,"timeElapsed":644333},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980856333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5376,"timeElapsed":649710},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980859500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3166,"timeElapsed":652877},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980866460,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6958,"timeElapsed":659836},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980870725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4264,"timeElapsed":664102},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980894628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":22617,"timeElapsed":688005},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980900455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5826,"timeElapsed":693832},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3296,"timeElapsed":697130},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980907166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3412,"timeElapsed":700543},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980913636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6468,"timeElapsed":707013},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980916299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2661,"timeElapsed":709676},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980919513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3213,"timeElapsed":712890},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980922188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2674,"timeElapsed":715565},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980925802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3612,"timeElapsed":719179},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980929505,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3702,"timeElapsed":722882},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980938802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":8251,"timeElapsed":732179},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980941095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2292,"timeElapsed":734472},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980944119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3023,"timeElapsed":737496},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980947613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3493,"timeElapsed":740990},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980961319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":13705,"timeElapsed":754696},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980965543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4223,"timeElapsed":758920},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980968561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3016,"timeElapsed":761938},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980970746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2184,"timeElapsed":764123},{"subjectID":"zjjzj85t6r","prolificID":"67252f59aafd74848a310025","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b26365597e50cafa01ae","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980974104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3356,"timeElapsed":767481}]